Guide to the Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS.223.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Contact Sheets, 1918-2006
  - Subseries B: Contact Sheets without Shoot Numbers
    - Unidentified contact sheets, undated (Box 36, Folder 61)
    - Unidentified contact sheets, undated (Box 36, Folder 62)
    - Unidentified contact sheets, undated (Box 36, Folder 63)